(All places, names, organizations, groups...)
(and religions in this drama are fictitious.)
Try this. It's delicious.
Okay.
The landlady made this. Try it.
I don't know if it's because I just saw a dead cat,
but it tastes weird.
I guess it's not your cup of tea.
Well... It's not.
I guess you're not into this part.
- What? - I have other parts. You want some?
It's late. Why don't we just drink and go in?
That's weird. It's some good meat.
Why are you so startled?
You think this is human meat or something?
I'll get going now. I have work tomorrow.
Okay.
- Goodnight. - Okay.
He finally closed his door.
I guess that pervert listens to the lady at least.
That's strange. It's tasty meat.
It's a shame he doesn't know that.
Gosh, I guess he's sensitive.
It's just my taste.
Should I add some MSG?
Then the meat's original taste will disappear.
You're right.
That's a relief. It's still intact.
It's exactly like the photo.
What was that expression anyway?
(Episode 4: Mental Derangement)
Hey, hey.
What?
- Back there. - What?
Look behind you.
Where?
Do you want to die?
You told me to look behind.
- You lunatic. - Drive! Look the other way!
Gosh.
I'm so scared.
It's not 13 cats.
Pardon?
I only killed one.
Hello.
Could you lower the volume?
What? I can't hear you.
Please turn down the music.
Okay.
What's wrong, ma'am?
Those kids were strange ever since they were born.
Your left taillight is out.
It's too dangerous to drive around at night like that.
Make sure to get it repaired tomorrow.
Gosh.
I wonder who did that. I'm so upset.
Anyway...
He said he was scared.
Sir.
We're going to check the back of your car.
Why?
I just need to check.
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
Take a look.
That's from food waste.
It's dangerous to drive with your taillight out,
so please get it repaired tomorrow.
- Okay. - Goodbye, then.
Don't police officers patrol in teams of two?
What?
You're alone.
(Police)
My brother and I always move around together.
It's you, the BB gun.
Can we leave now?
- Sure, you may. - Goodbye, ma'am.
Are you going back to the studio?
Yes. Why?
Nothing. Goodbye.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sir.
Gosh, it's already late. I should sleep.
That was so funny.
Now that the thug is gone, it's their world.
Gosh.
Anyway, I'm glad I got the plot going.
Right. I should write a bit every day.
Did the foreigner who used to live here stick those on?
Sergeant Jo?
Sergeant Jo, what are you doing there?
Would you like some?
It's human meat.
Grandma.
Thank you, young lady.
I'm going to work now.
- Young lady. - Yes?
My husband is nice.
Please find my husband.
Please find him.
I'll find him.
You didn't go to school yet?
I'm too old for school.
Good for you, Dad. You're a high school student now.
- Are you teasing me? - Yes.
- Go to work. - Okay.
- Watch out for cars. - Yes.
I'll be back.
Grandma, I'm going to work.
Bye.
- Be careful. - Okay.
That young lady has a very likable face.
Of course. She's your granddaughter.
Dr. Seo. Hello.
It's been a while. I guess you've been busy lately.
- Yes. Hello. - I rarely get to see you nowadays.
Hello, Se Yeon.
She gets shy around people.
Bye.
By the way, are you available this weekend?
The women's association is going to the nursing home for an event.
No, I mean to volunteer.
Just like the other time, will you be up for checking their...
I was wondering if you could check their teeth.
Excuse me. Hello?
Yes, ma'am. I hope Hak Soo is well.
Yes.
I'll call you later. Yes.
I'm sorry. Will you be available for that?
I have another appointment this weekend.
- I'm sorry. - I see.
- Help us out next time then. - Sure.
See you around, Se Yeon.
You always get shy whenever you see the dentist.
That man is scary.
Oh, right.
I should do this every day.
Why don't you calm down? We have a newcomer.
It didn't look like he was going to leave this place.
Darn it.
I'll kill you.
What did you say?
Just let it go.
If I take him seriously, I'll stoop to his level.
- Hello. - Who are you?
- I came by here the other day. - You're that police officer.
- Right. - My goodness.
You look so young without your uniform on.
You look so pretty too.
Are you going out?
I'm volunteering for senior citizens who live alone today.
I see. You're doing a good deed.
I guess you had always volunteered at places.
Pardon?
It didn't sound like this was your first time.
My gosh, is that why?
When I go out, beggars cling onto me.
By the way, what brings you here? Are you here to see me?
I just wanted to ask you a question.
- This man. - I was about to leave.
This is the man who used to live in Unit 303.
You know that this guy went missing, right?
Of course, I was the one who reported him missing.
A man who used to live in this room killed himself.
- Missing? He didn't kill himself? - Hey.
- Are you going to work? - Yes.
So what is it? Did you find him?
No. We're still looking for him.
You still haven't found him?
Gosh, this is so upsetting.
I tried not to bring this up with you.
But don't you think you police are being irresponsible?
Gosh, I can't believe you still haven't found him.
That's why I'm trying to investigate this with all of my resources.
How can you find him with just your resources?
Just send the patrol cars during the night here.
Some guys pee all over this place. It's causing me headaches.
Young man, why are you still here?
Gosh, were you waiting for me?
No, I forgot something upstairs.
- Hey, I'm late for my appointment. - Yes?
- I'll get going now. - Okay.
- Bye. - Call me later.
- Okay. Bye. - Okay? Call me when you find him.
Where did he go after leaving all of his stuff?
My gosh. I got nothing.
Hello.
Hello. We met in front of Eden Studio earlier.
- Pardon? - We met earlier.
Yes.
Right. Can we talk for a second?
I'm on my way to work now.
That's great. I can give you a ride.
- I'll just walk. - It will only take a minute.
Please? Here.
I can drop you off at the bus stop, right?
Yes. Over there.
By the way, how long have you been living at the studio?
Four days.
I overheard the conversation earlier.
So the foreigner who used to live at the studio went missing?
Yes, but everyone seems very nonchalant about it.
Was there anybody else that was reported missing?
Did someone from the studio disappear again?
According to the landlady,
he did move out of the studio.
But it was odd that it was so sudden.
And it didn't look like he'd leave any time soon either.
Besides, a detective came to the studio a while ago.
- A detective? - Yes.
Can I get the detective's number?
His business card...
I did get his business card, but it's at my office.
I'll give it to you later.
Okay. Here's my number.
I'd really appreciate it if you call me.
Please give me a call.
- Bye. - Bye.
Okay.
How nice.
It looks like your ancestor had lived a virtuous life.
Hello. You have a very likable face.
You must be new to the neighborhood.
Hello, ma'am.
Your face is glowing.
It looks like your ancestor had lived a virtuous life.
Do you live in the neighborhood? You must be going somewhere nice.
Is there something on my face?
No.
Do you really think my face is glowing?
That's fascinating.
Of course.
By the way, don't you have a lot of sick people around you lately?
My gosh, how did you know that?
You really are something else!
Let's not talk about this on the street. Why don't we...
go to a cafe nearby and discuss it over a cup of tea?
You know what? Let's not do that. Let's go to my house.
It's just over the hill.
I'll serve you a nice cup of tea.
Really?
So I wasn't mistaken.
You really are a generous woman.
Let's go to my house and tell me all about it. Okay?
- Sure. - Come with me.
You're really gifted.
Thank you. Goodbye.
(I'm near Daehangno on business and want to...)
(drop by and see you. Are you free?)
(Ji Eun)
(I'm on the way. Fourth floor, right?)
(Ji Eun, wait...)
(Ji Eun, wait, I'll come...)
Hey.
- Wow. - It's been a while.
- You got so pretty. - What?
Come here.
- Say hi. - Hello.
This is Jong Woo's girlfriend I mentioned.
Isn't she pretty?
Everyone is at that age.
Come on, sir.
Yu Jung's pretty too.
You're even prettier.
Really?
Yes, well, Yu Jung performed on stage.
Don't mind us and get to work.
Come here, have a coffee.
No, thanks. I have to go. I just dropped by to see him.
We haven't met since he moved to Seoul.
Really?
Don't work him too hard.
What do you think I... Hey, tell her.
He's nice to me.
- See? - As if.
I really have to go. I'll call.
Can't you stay for a coffee?
I really only came by to see Jong Woo.
I have a boss to tiptoe around too.
You're in the premier league.
Look at us. We're a neighborhood team.
I could lose my job any day. Bye.
Can I go downstairs to see her off?
Actually, I'd like to...
Don't even ask. See her off.
Okay then. Let's go.
Wait, wait.
Good for you, Jong Woo.
You have a girlfriend and all.
I'm jealous. Darn it.
I missed your text.
I didn't call.
Walk in the shade.
Actually...
This is for you.
- What is it? - It's...
I went to have my laptop fixed and they were doing a lucky draw.
I threw a dart.
This is actually...
the worst prize they had.
But... But...
It suited you.
Okay, fine.
You said you'd walk me to give me this?
That too.
How cute.
I'll hang it on my bag. Thanks.
Sure.
Oh, that guy in the corner. Is he your mentor?
Yes.
He was really weird.
- Was he? - He didn't even say hi.
- I was so embarrassed. - I see.
- Can we meet this weekend? - So...
We should.
- Okay. I have to go. - Wait.
There's a taxi. Take that.
Thanks.
- Call me. - Okay.
Bye. Take care.
Am I too tired because I didn't sleep? I'm seeing things.
Jong Woo.
Ji Eun looks like she's in heat, doesn't she?
What?
I mean I think she likes you a lot.
Jae Ho.
Don't talk like that about Ji Eun.
It's offensive.
Don't get so worked up about a joke.
Yu Jung.
Do you think I went too far?
You, Sang Man?
Pardon?
Yes, Jong Woo, you overreacted.
It was just a joke.
Right?
See? You're the only one acting up.
See? I told you he's weird.
You're weird.
Let's go out for lunch.
The lunatics.
Here.
This is all I have to offer my special guest.
It's fine. Thank you.
Who is this lady?
Hello.
I met her on the street.
She's very smart.
I brought her over to ask her a few things.
Do you want to join us?
Sit down.
You can speak freely.
What do you see in him?
This should be fun.
Your ear is split in two.
I see someone else.
A brother or a sister?
My gosh. That's amazing.
See? I told you she's very good.
Tell me something else.
You'll have an unfortunate year.
An unfortunate year.
- That's bad. - What's that?
What is that?
It means bad luck.
Stay away from me.
Your bad luck might rub off on me.
Are you saying I'll have rotten luck?
It's not that. It's...
It's because of your sins and bad karma.
If you pray with us...
I sinned? Is that it?
You sinned. That's bad.
You said you're good at reading fortunes.
Then tell me. Is it a man...
or a woman?
What?
The person you talked about earlier...
that you said you could see.
I think it's a man.
Then... Then...
is that person older or younger than me?
Younger, maybe?
Wrong!
You didn't get anything right.
I should go.
Stop.
This lady's weird.
Lady. Do you know why so many people around me are sick?
What?
It's because I make them sick.
Didn't you know?
Don't hurt me.
You talk about fortunes when you can't even see your own?
Why you...
Last night, a hiker found a body part in a black plastic bag.
What's going on?
Some people are worse than dogs.
Not even dogs do that.
It's because they don't execute...
Did you see that news a few days ago?
There was a hydrochloric acid attack.
- Yes, I heard. - They caught the guy.
Must you talk about that during lunch?
Just listen.
The criminal was the CEO of a small company.
He made lots of donations...
and had a good reputation and a family.
Then what, does a criminal...
have "I'm a killer" on his forehead?
That's what I'm saying.
Such people look normal on the outside.
That's right.
I saw a guy get half beaten to death when I met Jong Woo for drinks.
- Really? - Yes.
One guy was out of his mind and raining punches.
Jong Woo stopped him.
He's quite the psycho himself.
Good for you.
Jong Woo, have some raw beef.
You probably don't get this at the studio.
You need the nutrients.
The meat here is amazing.
Are you okay?
He must not feel well.
Did he almost puke at my face?
It can't be that.
That's not entirely unlikely.
That was mean. I am the CEO, you know.
Just eat.
I know people like you.
I met someone like you during my military service.
They act nice but criticize behind people's back.
If you are trying to win sympathy...
with that pretty face,
it won't work on me.
What are you talking about?
Should I kill him?
You should kill him.
I am really annoyed now.
By the way, how is our intern doing?
He is not doing much.
Come on. You need to take better care of him.
Think of him as your brother.
I saw him lost like a stray dog once.
He doesn't know anything.
Shouldn't he have more experience to be in the field?
That is why you need to teach him.
- Jong Woo, are you okay? - Yes.
It breaks my heart that you are sick...
when you live in such a horrible studio.
Do you need some fresh air?
That studio does not have a good ventilation system.
There are practically no windows.
Once the air goes in, there's no way out.
Did you finish already?
Why don't you go in first? I need to speak with Jong Woo.
What is it? A bromance?
Are you really okay? Do you need to go home early?
It's fine. It's just indigestion.
How can a young man like you be so weak?
- Does that studio provide dinner? - Jae Ho.
Can you not talk about the studio in front of other people?
Why is it dripping so much?
- Why? Are you embarrassed? - No.
- That is how everyone starts. - Just...
Can you just not talk about it in front of others?
- What? - You have never lived there.
What kind of attitude is this?
- Sorry. I just don't feel well. - Darn it.
It is too dirty for me to finish.
Yun Jong Woo. Let's be professionals, all right?
At work, I am the CEO, and you are just an employee.
Have you ever seen an employee being rude to the CEO?
- You... - I am not trying to be rude...
Stop calling my name.
You need to be in better control of your emotions.
There is no point in being nice to people.
Look at this sweat.
What is so scary that you have to wet yourself?
The deity you trust so much will come and save you.
Isn't that right?
Do you remember me now?
It's me. Bok Soon.
The one who ate too much. Eom Bok Soon.
Do you remember now?
I remembered you the moment I saw you.
Isn't life so interesting?
Let me take care of my business. Have fun with her.
Later.
Shall we begin?
(Cha Sung Ryeol)
Hello?
I am the person you met in front of the studio this morning.
Hello, Jong Woo.
I just sent a picture of the business card.
Thank you.
Please check that. I need to get back to work, so...
- Hang on. - Sure.
If I need anything,
can I call you?
Sure. I need to get back to work. I will hang up now.
- Thank you. - Goodbye, Officer.
Officer? Are you in trouble?
It's nothing.
Of course, it is something. I can see it.
- You can talk to me. - It really is nothing.
- Let's get back. - Are you still angry?
I can tell it in your voice.
You think we are still in some college clubs? No.
I am the CEO that pays you, and you are my employee.
You need to control your emotions better.
Hey.
- Smile. - What?
I said, smile.
Why are you doing this to me, Jae Ho?
Jae Ho?
- Mr. Shin. - You think I am joking?
I said smile.
Wait.
Wait. Let's make this work, got it?
Yes, sir.
The person you have called is unavailable right now...
(Cha Sung Ryeol)
This is Lee Kwang Jae from District Investigation Team.
Hello, my name is Soh Jung Hwa,
an officer of the Eunhye Patrol Division.
Why did you call us?
Well...
I was hoping to get in touch with Detective Cha Sung Ryeol.
His phone is turned off.
Detective Cha?
We can't reach him either because he is on vacation.
Vacation?
Yes. He didn't pick up our calls for days too.
- Why are you looking for him? - Well...
Detective Cha met someone...
at a studio that was within our jurisdiction.
And that person is now missing, so I was hoping to talk to him.
A studio?
I will pass on the message once I get hold of him.
That will be great. Thank you.
Thank you.
- Give that to me. - Geez!
- Give it to me. - You scared me! You should knock.
Knock, knock. Give it to me.
(Eunhye Patrol Division)
Here.
Definitely with an engineering background.
A goddess of the engineering department?
- Mr. Park. - What is it?
Before you came here, you were in the Criminal Division, right?
Yes, I was.
If that's the case, what does it mean...
when a detective suddenly isn't picking up his calls?
Why do you want to know?
Do you remember the guy who came in because of the dead cat?
With a gun?
- BB gun? - Yes.
Two people went missing...
from his studio.
And a detective who was on his way to meet one of them...
is now no longer picking up his calls.
Isn't it strange?
That can happen.
Some detectives, when they are into a case,
they might be unreachable for some time.
He will resurface again a few days later.
I don't think so.
It is really strange. I can really feel it.
Just a feeling?
How does a newbie just have a feeling?
A patrol division...
isn't a place for investigation.
If you joined the police to investigate, think again.
Don't get all nosy.
Focus on your job.
You have some change, right?
Why?
What?
You said that I should just focus on my job.
This is for my overtime pay. Thanks.
Overtime pay?
That was five dollars!
And I didn't join the police to do investigations.
I joined to help people. I'll get going now.
See you tomorrow.
Funny kid.
Jong Woo, aren't you going home?
- I... - Hey,
why don't you go on a date with your pretty girlfriend?
I'm seeing her on the weekend. I'll finish up a bit more work.
If anyone saw this,
they'd think that you do everything around here.
You're doing that again.
- Be kind. - Okay.
Everyone, go home.
Yu Jung, what about a beer after work?
I'm busy today. I'll get going now.
I have a family dinner to attend.
See you tomorrow.
All right. Eat dinner with your family.
I'm just going to drink alone today.
(Living expenses per month)
I can only save 250 dollars a month even if spend as little as possible.
Goodness.
How am I going to find a new place and move in?
Hey, when does the draft of the poster design come out?
The draft copy?
Probably sometime early next month.
- I'll let you know when I find out. - Is that right?
We need to get it done when the actors aren't busy.
We need to plan it in advance, so Ji Eun,
please check all the actors' schedules.
Ji Eun?
Ji Eun!
What are you thinking about?
Why are you zoning out?
I asked you to check on all the actors' schedules.
Yes, ma'am.
You were thinking about what to have for dinner tonight, right?
Unbelievable.
Ji Eun loves eating, don't you think so?
You heard it, right? We need to film the draft,
so please check and coordinate with the actors' schedules.
Yes, I will do that.
And we're grabbing a beer tonight.
Wait, you're meeting your boyfriend.
No, I'm free tonight.
Is that so? Join us then.
Sure, sounds good.
You don't have to come if you're busy.
What do I say?
Hello.
We'll get going now.
- Okay. - See you tomorrow.
Sorry for everything today.
It's fine. See you tomorrow.
- Bye. - Good night.
I'm sorry you're stuck here because of me.
It's fine.
You look quite tired as well.
There's just so much work to do lately.
Cats dying, people missing...
Sorry, I'm talking too much.
- Sorry. - It's fine, you can sit down.
Okay.
So someone keeps killing cats?
Exactly.
What kind of a person treats stray cats like that?
Once, I read in a book...
that murderers apparently...
begin off with murdering animals first.
It might not be just a mean joke.
Do you think so too?
Why? Are you suspecting anyone?
I can't pinpoint a particular person.
The people at the studio seem quite suspicious, though.
Sorry, I'm talking too much again.
Look at me.
Sorry, I forgot to bring your patient chart.
- Hold on. - Okay.
(Yu Spring Dentist)
- Hi. - Jung Hwa,
you know the surveillance camera that we tracked and downloaded?
I need to get my hands on that and watch it.
I was wondering if you could grab it for me.
Right now?
Yes, I'm in a rush. Where are you?
I'm at the dentist right now.
That's good, you're not too far then.
What about Hyun Oh?
He's far away to see his family.
I'm sorry I'm making you work after working hours.
It's fine.
Sorry, I have something to do.
I'm sorry I made you stay and I'm leaving.
It's fine, you're a busy person.
Sorry.
But make sure to visit as soon as you feel pain.
Okay, thank you.
- Get home safely. - Thanks.
It's the same.
His legs were thin like sticks. His legs were thinner than mine.
I just don't get it.
But...
Ji Eun, it looks like it's your boyfriend. You can pick up.
It's fine.
Just pick up, don't let it ring.
Okay.
Whenever I meet new guys...
Hey.
Are you working overtime again?
Yes, what about you?
I have a work dinner.
My assistant manager wanted a drink.
I see.
Why do you sound so glum? Did something happen?
What is it? Tell me.
Are they talking about me behind my back right now?
What?
Nothing. What were you saying?
Ji Eun,
you know the studio that I'm staying at?
The people here are weird.
One guy keeps stammering and bickering.
And another guy keeps cursing at me.
I don't know who it is,
but someone keeps breaking into my room.
Jong Woo,
how many of the people who live there do you think are normal?
It'll only tire you out to act so sensitively to them.
Also, I think you should be more firm at work.
Did you know that?
Being a kind person isn't a compliment anymore.
Okay.
Sorry, I went overboard.
No, you're right.
I guess I'm being overly sensitive.
You can head inside, people are waiting for you.
You're not upset, are you?
I'm not.
I'll message you on my way home.
Okay.
There you are!
- Are you coming home now? - Yes.
Come in for a second.
- What? - It won't take long.
Come in.
- Why? - Look at you sweating.
- It's fine. - You need to shower.
Drink this. It'll cool you down.
Why did you call me in here?
I just have a question. Drink up.
- Isn't it good? - What is it?
Well...
- This morning, - Yes?
I saw you talking to that female police officer.
Is something wrong?
This morning?
Yes, did you guys talk about something serious?
Something serious?
It's nothing much.
But as you know, several of our residents have moved out.
I have to make ends meet, you know?
If weird rumors spread, my business will take a hit.
I see.
- You understand, right? - Of course.
- I should go back in. - All right.
All right. Give that to me.
You must've bought something.
- You should take a shower. - Okay.
How's Unit 303?
Come on. This isn't my first rodeo.
The drug is kicking in.
There's nothing to worry about.
Will you take care...
of Unit 303 tonight?
That looks tasty. Good luck with that.
Thanks.
Oh, right.
- Ma'am. - Yes?
- Why did you do it? - Do what?
The woman on the fourth floor.
What is it?
Are you going to kill me too for being reckless?
Of course, not.
You're special.
Try being cooped up in here.
You become raring.
Right. I trust you.
Goodbye.
I should add a lot of MSG.
This feels strange.
Why does my head hurt whenever I come here?
I feel nauseous.
See? I told you.
I told you not to be a show-off!
Kill him. Kill him.
- Shut it, you scumbag! - Kill him.
Jong Woo,
how many of the people who live there do you think are normal?
It'll only tire you out to act so sensitively to them.
- Kill him. - Also, I think you should be...
- Kill him. - more firm at work.
If you are trying to win sympathy with that pretty face,
Being a kind person isn't a compliment anymore.
it won't work on me.
- Kill him. - Being a kind person...
isn't a compliment anymore.
Kill him.
- Kill him. - Did you know?
Being a kind person isn't a compliment anymore.
Am I having indigestion?
I feel so exhausted.
Did something ruin my mood today?
Did I take drugs?
What's wrong with my body?
What's going on?
What could it be all of a sudden?
(Stranger from Hell)
Ma'am, I think someone broke into my room.
Come out. Come out right now!
I think you've become strange ever since you came to Seoul.
Is something going on at the studio?
Did anything else happen at the studio?
The fourth floor...
I just heard a noise from this floor.
Ever since the fire, no one has been living on the fourth floor.
You think you're not suited for this place, right?
Unit 303 seems to be meeting...
with that policewoman often.
Are you okay?